expert-lender.com 2013-09-01

# Home Loan Expert Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Home Loan Expert knows that you value your privacy. Because of this, we want you to know that we view your security as a major concern, and that it is important to us. We make every effort to ensure that your information remains confidential. Home Loan Expert has dedicated a large portion of electronic, physical, and procedural safeguards to our clients' personal information safety.

**PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION**

We are committed to protecting your privacy and providing a secure online experience. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with U.S. standards to transmit and store information about you.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**

We collect some information about you to help us serve your financial needs, to provide you with quality products and services and to fulfill legal and regulatory requirements. We consider all information about you in our possession to be personal information, even if you cease to be a customer. The personal information we collect about you may include among other things nonpersonally identifiable information such as URL, browser type, and TCP/IP information. We do not collect any personal information about you including your name, address, phone number, your financial situation.

**PARTIES TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE**

Some of our services may be provided by third-party service providers, and we reserve the right to share your nonpublic information with them. You may not opt-out of this sharing of information if you apply through our website. Finally, we may share the nonpublic information we collect with companies or organizations with whom we have a marketing or other agency relationship, generally to offer you services in which we believe you may have an interest.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to change or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notification. Please check the website frequently to apprise yourself of any changes that may affect you. The posting of any changes will be the only notice that you will receive regarding any such amendments or changes in policy.

**"COOKIE" POLICY**

To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want, we collect aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. We do not track individuals' use of the site. When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies). If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from this website, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

**CHILDREN AND THE INTERNET**

We do not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information from consumers under the age of eighteen. You must be at least eighteen years of age to obtain services from this site.

**WHAT IF I DISAGREE WITH THE TERMS OF YOUR PRIVACY POLICY?**

If you disagree with the terms of our privacy policy, please do not use our website or provide us with any of your personal information.

* * *
